QUESTIONS = [
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 1?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 0
    },
   {
        "question": "Вопрос 2?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 3?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 4?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 5?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 6?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 7?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 8?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 9?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Вопрос 10?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3","4"],
        "correct_option": 1
    }
]
